DAVID COPPOCK

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

DETAILS

Enola, PA 717.215.5968 autosavedave@gmail.com github.com/autosavedave

SKILLS

FRONTEND

HTML5, CSS, Javascript, Query, Bootstrap, Bulma, React, Material UI, three.js, react-threefiber

BACKEND

Node, Express, MySQL, MongoDB, Graph QL, Handlebars, Google Firebase

SOFTWARE

Insomnia, Game Maker Studio 2, Adobe Animate

OBJECTIVE

Experienced scientist and lab manager looking to join your team as a recently certified full-stack web developer with numerous transferable skills. 20 years of experience making 2D games for PC and mobile have confirmed a lasting interest in this work. Creative thinker with the ability to manage wide-ranging client demands to build innovative, elegant solutions.

EDUCATION



University of Pennsylvania LPS Coding Bootcamp, Philadelphia, PA 2022 Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development



Carnegie Mellon University, Pittsburgh, PA Bachelor of Science: Chemistry 2010

RELATED EXPERIENCE

Strange New Methods | Philadelphia, PA **Independent Game Developer**

March 2013 - Oct. 2017

- · Oversaw game design from creation to publication for innovative 2D game
- · Composed, recorded, and produced music for games
- · Solicited, compiled, and implemented user testing feedback
- · Designed game systems and mechanics for three games
- · Created graphic and audio assets for games
- Developed games for Android, iOS, HTML5, and PC

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

GlaxoSmithKline (GSK) | Carlisle, PA **Quality Insurance Inspector**

Jan 2020-May 2020

- · Conducted inspections of manufacturing equipment before operator use
- · Calibrated equipment used in quality assurance procedures
- · Sampled and inspected product to ensure cGMP and SOP compliance
- · Conducted routine reviews of records to ensure cGMP compliance

DAVID COPPOCK

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY (CONT.)

B Positive Plasma | Glassboro, NJ/ Cherry Hill, NJ

Assistant Quality Assurance Manager

Feb 2019-April 2019

- Oversaw the receipt and Investigation of over 100 donor and employee concerns
- · Wrote audit reports and coordinated corrective action in response to findings
- · Coordinated corrective action for a wide range of policy violations for over 50 staff members
- · Performed facility, equipment, and staff audits to ensure SOP and cGMP compliance
- · Prepared and performed final review of all outbound sample and product shipments; approximately 30,000 units
- · Performed calibration and qualification of center equipment

Assistant Center Manager

Sept. 2018-Feb. 2019

- · Directly supervised 70-80 full-time medical professionals and administrative staff
- · Oversaw the interview, hiring, and onboarding of all staff positions
- · Managed staff operations, schedules, training, and performance reviews
- · Created Excel VBA macro to simplify and expedite review of plasma collection records
- · Handled positive donor test results and counseled donors on positive results
- · Reviewed records to ensure regulatory, SOP, and cGMP compliance

Laboratory Coordinator

April 2018-Sept. 2018

- · Supervised 12 laboratory technicians
- · Inspected cases of product in accordance with regulatory requirements before shipment
- · Documented incidents and deviations in the NextGen issue tracking system
- · Worked with QA and management to implement improvements in laboratory efficiency
- · Trained laboratory technicians and medical assistants on SOP's
- Performed all B Positive laboratory technician duties

Laboratory Technician

Oct. 2017-April 2018

- · Performed quality control on laboratory equipment and walk-in freezer
- · Processed collections per PPTA, SOP, and cGMP requirements
- · Extracted samples from plasma collections for testing
- · Packed plasma bottles and samples for shipment
- Maintained organization of walk-in freezer used for plasma storage

Clean Harbors Environmental Services, Inc. | Bridgeport, NJ

Lab Pack Chemist

June 2012-Feb. 2013

- · Managed hazardous waste transportation and disposal for more than 30 sites
- · Acted as lead lab pack chemist on high profile sites; recognized for safe practices and professionalism
- · Prepared paperwork for transportation of hazardous waste
- · Segregated waste by hazard class for lab packs
- · Determined all applicable DOT and EPA waste codes for lab pack items
- · Consolidated hazardous waste into bulk containers

Emory University, Environmental Health & Safety | Atlanta, GA

Environmental Compliance Specialist

Oct. 2010 - Feb. 2012

- · Created an emergency preparedness analysis Excel VBA macro
- · Collected and classified chemical waste by DOT and EPA waste codes for disposal
- · Oversaw the collection and processing of radioactive waste for decay and disposal
- · Served in on-call role for emergency response with spills and exposures.
- · Performed weekly radiation contamination surveys and weekly inspections for 8 radioactive waste facilities